=====================================================
				Print Emojis using Python
=====================================================
Emojis are used to express our emotions while writing a message or any piece of text. If you want to learn how to display emojis in the output using the Python programming language we use emoji module
============================
Print Emojis using Python
============================
Smiling, thumbs up, and the heart emoji are some of the emojis we often use while texting our friends or colleagues. It’s possible to print any emoji using the Python programming language. To print emojis using Python, you need to install the emoji module in your Python virtual environment. You can easily install it by using the pip command on your terminal or command prompt as mentioned below:
=======================
pip install emoji
=======================
The emoji.emojize() method helps you write the description of any emoji inside “::” while writing a piece of text. Below are examples of descriptions of some of the popular emojis:

:thumbs_up:
:red_heart:
:smiling_face:
You can use the description of any emoji inside “::” to print the emoji using Python. You can find the description of all the emojis here(https://carpedm20.github.io/emoji/). Now let’s have a look at an example of how to print emojis using Python:

import emoji
print(emoji.emojize("I love reading books:books:"))
print(emoji.emojize("Some people have a very sensitive heart:red_heart:, please be kind with them.:hibiscus:"))
OUTPUT
---------------
I love reading books📚
Some people have a very sensitive heart❤️, please be kind with them.🌺
So this is how you can use emojis and print them in your output using the Python programming language.
========================================================
Summary
Emojis are used to express our emotions while writing a message or any piece of text. To print any emoji using Python, you need to install the emoji module in your Python virtual environment. 
